barcodesinc.com 2019-04-23

# Privacy and Security Policy - BarcodesInc

Effective Date: April 1, 2006

Thank you for visiting our web site and reviewing our Privacy Policy. BarcodesInc is committed to protecting your privacy. Our business depends on the trust our customers place in us. It is our policy to protect your Personal Information (as defined below) and to use it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In this policy, "Site" shall mean www.barcodesinc.com and "we", "us", and "our" shall mean BarcodesInc.

## Information We Collect From You

We automatically collect information about your Internet connection, such as:

  * The name of the Internet domain you used to access the Internet;
  * The IP address of the web site from which you linked directly to our Site, and if from an internet search engine, the keywords that were used for that search;
  * The type of browser you are using; 
  * The date and time you access our Site; and
  * The pages you visit.

This information ("Non-Personal Information") does not identify you personally. We use this Non-Personal Information to monitor the effectiveness of the Site, identify areas of interest and consider potential improvements to the Site.

When placing an order, requesting a quote, or in certain other communications with us, we ask you to provide contact information (including name, shipping address, telephone number, and e-mail address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date, and billing address) (collectively "Personal Information"). By providing such information, you consent to our collection and use of it, as described in this Privacy Policy. We do not collect any Personal Information about you when you visit the Site unless you give us that information.

## Use of Your Personal Information

We use Personal Information obtained from you to provide products and services, respond to your questions or inquiries, identify customer prospects, track purchasing histories and areas of customer interest, and consider potential improvements to our Site.

We may occasionally send you promotional offers or product updates. If you do not wish to receive these communications, you may opt out of future e-mails by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in the e-mail.

We may provide links to other sites of interest. We do not review or endorse the content of these sites or guarantee that they will abide by this Privacy Policy. Your use of such linked sites is subject to the terms and conditions and privacy policies of the providers of those sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each Site that collects Personal Information.

Please note that your use of the Site and services is subject to our Terms and Conditions of Use which you may access from our Home Page or other Site pages by clicking on Terms of Use.

## Sharing Your Information

We do not sell or trade Personal Information to marketing companies or information brokers. We will only disclose your Personal Information in the following circumstances without first obtaining your consent:

  * We may provide Personal Information when requested to do so in certain types of legal or law enforcement proceedings. 
  * We may buy or sell business assets or be acquired by or acquire other companies or BarcodesInc institutions. In such transactions, Personal Information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In addition, in the event we merge or consolidate with another institution, your Personal Information may be transferred to the successor BarcodesInc institution.
  * We may use third party suppliers and service providers to facilitate our services, and they may have access to Personal Information. For example, we may outsource one or more aspects of our Site to a supplier or service provider who performs services according to our requirements. In these cases we will restrict through written agreements how these suppliers or service providers may use or disclose the Personal Information to which they have access.

Please remember that, although we endeavor to select only reputable companies who share our commitment to customer privacy, we are in no way responsible for the actions or policies of these other organizations. 

## Use of Cookies

The use of cookies enables us to enhance your visits to the Site. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your web browser. The help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, but this will limit your ability to use some features. Cookies enable us to recognize your browser and provide features that are tailored to your needs.

We may use information from cookies for purposes of planning and tracking, as well as assessing the technical function of the Site. We may also use cookies to track information about which pages you visit within the Site to help us gauge the effectiveness of the Site or our content.

## Security Measures

We work hard to protect the security of your information. Our order processing system protects your Personal Information through the use of Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") encryption. While we strive to protect your information by using SSL and other measures to protect our system, such security cannot be ensured. Consequently, we do not ensure or warrant the security of information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk. If your communication to us includes confidential information, you may want to contact us by using telephone, fax, or regular mail.

## Children and Parents

We do not offer or provide products and services for children. If you are under 18, you may use our Site only with involvement of a parent or guardian. We do not intend to collect Personal Information from children. If your child has submitted Personal Information and you would like to request that such information be removed, you may contact us by one of the methods listed below, and we will honor your request.

## Changes to this Statement

We may change this Privacy Statement from time-to-time. If we do make a change, we will post the revised Privacy Statement on this Site. We encourage you to review this Privacy Statement periodically. Questions, comments or complaints about our privacy policies should be submitted to us by one of the methods listed above.

Thank you for visiting our site. If you have any questions, or if you are unsatisfied with us for any reason, please contact us toll-free at 1-800-351-9962 or e-mail us at [customerservice@barcodesinc.com](mailto:customerservice@barcodesinc.com).
